Guide to the Protestant Episcopal Bishops Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, Series I
  - American Bishops
    - Keator, Frederic William 1855-1924, (Olympia, Wash.) (7), 1901-1903, 1913, 1919 (Box 4, Folder 194)
    - Keeler, Stephen Edwards 1887-, (Minn.) (3), 1937 (Box 4, Folder 195)
    - Kemerer, Benjamin T. (Duluth, Minn.) (1), undated (Box 4, Folder 196)
    - Kemp, James 1764-1827, (Md.) (6), 1818, 1822, 1824, 1826 (Box 4, Folder 197)
    - Kemper, Jackson 1789-1870, (Wisc.) (7), 1850, 1855-1856, 1865 (Box 4, Folder 198)
    - Kendrick, John Mills 1836-1911, (N.M., Ariz.) (6), 1889, 1895, 1904, 1907 (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - Kerfoot, John Barrett 1816-1881, (Penn.) (7), 1841-1842, 1854, 1866, 1872, 1876 (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - Kinsman, Frederick Joseph 1868-1944, (Del.) (10), 1908-1910, 1912, 1916 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - Kinsolving, George Herbert 1849-1928, (Texas) (7), 1894, 1900, 1903, 1907, undated (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Kinsolving, Lucien Lee (Brazil) (5), 1902-1903, 1907, 1910 (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Kip, William Ingraham 1811-1893, (Cal.) (6), 1836, 1944, 1857, 1886-1887 (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - Knickerbacker, David Buel 1833-1894, (Ind.) (7), 1875, 1889, 1891, 1893, undated (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Knight, Albion Williamson 1859-1936, (Cuba) (10), 1903, 1906, 1910, 1912, 1915-1916, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - Knight, Cyrus Frederick 1831-1891, (Milwaukee, Wisc.) (6), 1867, 1889-1891 (Box 4, Folder 207)
    - Knight, Edward Jennings 1864-1908, (W. Col.) (5) (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - Krischke, Egmont Machado (S.W. Brazil) (1), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Kroll, Leopold (Liberia) (2), 1938 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Larned, John Insley Blair (L.I., N.Y.) (1), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - Lawrence, William 1850-1941, (Mass.) (24), 1883, 1894, 1897, 1903, 1906, 1908, 1910-1911, 1915, 1919, 1923, 1930, 1937, undated (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - Lawrence, William Appleton 1889-, (W. Mass.) (7), 1937, 1941, undated (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - Lay, Henry Champlin 1823-1885, (Easton, Md.) (17), 1872-1874, 1876, 1878, 1880, 1882-1883 (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - Lee, Alfred 1807-1887, (Del.) (16), 1842, 1848, 1859-1860, 1862, 1865, 1872, 1878-1879, 1886 (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Lee, Henry Washington 1815-1874, (Iowa) (12), 1841, 1854, 1858, 1861-1863, 1865 (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - Leonard, Abiel 1848-1903, (Nev.& Utah;W.Col.), 1888-1890, 1892, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Leonard, William Andrew 1848-1930, (Ohio) (10), 1883, 1888-1889, 1899, 1909, 1915, 1919, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Lewis, William F. (Nev.) (1), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Lichtenberger, Arthur (Mo.) (1), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - Lines [Leines], Edwin Stevens 1845-1927, (Newark, N.J.) (12), 1903-1905, 1908, 1912, 1916-1917, 1919-1921 (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Littell, S. Harrington (Honolulu) (2), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Littlejohn, Abram Newkirk 1824-1901, (L.I., N.Y.) (13), 1874, 1878, 1882-1884, 1887, 1889, 1891, 1894-1895 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Lloyd, Arthur Selden 1857-1936, (Va.) (7), 1909, 1911-1913 (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Longley, Harry Sherman 1868-, (Iowa) (6), 1913, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - Ludlow, Theodore Russell (Newark, N.J.) (1), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 226)
    - Lyman, Theodore Benedict 1815-1893, (N.C.) (9), 1885-1887, 1889 (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - McCormick, John Newton 1863-, (W.Mich.) (9), 1906-1907, 1911, 1925, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - McCosky, Samuel Allen 1804-1886, (Micy.) (6), 1846, 1859, 1875, 1877 (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - McDowell, William George 1882-1938, (Ala.) (4), 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 230)
    - McElwain, Frank Arthur 1875-, (Minn.) (7), 1912-1914, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - McIlvaine, Charles Petitt 1799-1873, (Ohio) (18), 1823, 1839, 1844, 1851, 1854, 1863, 1865-1867, 1871, undated (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - McKim, John 1852-1936, (Tokyo) (5), 1903, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - McKinstry, Arthur Raymond 1895-, (Del.) (1), undated (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - McLaren, William Edward 1831-1905, (Chicago) (8), 1875, 1889, 1902, 1904 (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - McVickar, William Neilson 1854-1910, (R.I.) (8), 1876, 1898, 1902-1903, 1905 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - Mackay-Smith, Alexander 1850-1911, (Penn.) (6), 1902-1903, undated (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - Madison, James 1749-1812, (Va.) (4), 1789, 1804, 1807 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Mann, Alexander 1860-, (Pittsburg) (2), 1934, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Mann, Cameron 1851-1932, (N.Dak.) (6), 1902-1903, 1907, 1909, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Manning, William Thomas 1866-1949, (N.Y.) (26), 1915, 1921-1923, 1925-1926, 1929-1932, 1934-1935, 1937, 1939, undated (Box 5, Folder 241)
      - [Printed articles, clippings, etc., 1942, 1949] (10) (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Matthews, Paul 1866-, (N.J.) (4), 1915, 1919, 1935, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - Maxon, James Matthew 1875-1948, (Tenn.) (2), 1941 (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - Meade, William 1789-1862, (Va.) (23), 1844, 1846-1849, 1853-1856, 1858-1860, undated (Box 5, Folder 244)
      [The 1844 letter is written on the back of a 2p. printed statement concerning the Epis. Theol. school in Va.]
    - Melcher, Louis C. (1), undated (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - Mikell, Henry Judah 1873-, (Atlanta) (4), 1937-1938, undated (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Millspaugh, Frank Rosebrook 1848-1916, (Kansas) (7), 1900-1901, 1903, 1907 (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - Mitchell, Walter (Ariz.) (2), 1937, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 248)
    - Moore, Benjamin 1748-1816, (N.Y.) (4), 1796, 1810 (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - Moore, Harry Tunis (Dallas) (1), undated (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - Moore, Richard Channing 1762-1842, (Va.) (6), 1810, 1823, 1828, 1830, 1840 (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - Moreland, William Hall 1861-, (Sacramento) (8), 1903, 1906-1907, 1913, 1927, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - Morris, Benjamin Wistar 1819-1906, (Oregon)(10), 1874, 1880, 1883, 1887, 1890, 1896, 1898 (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - Morris, James Craik 1870-, (La.) (4), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 254)
    - Morrison, James Dow 1844, 1934, (Duluth, Minn.) (6), 1898, 1903, 1907, 1910 (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - Morrison, Theodore Nevin 1850-1929, (Iowa) (7), 1902-1903, 1910, 1915, 1919 (Box 5, Folder 256)
    - Mosher, Gouverneur Frank 1871-, (Philippines) (2), 1935, 1938 (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - Moulton, Arthur W. (Utah) (1), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 258)
    - Murray, John Gardner 1857-1929, (Md.) (8), 1909, 1915, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 259)
    - Neely, Henry Adams 1830-1899, (Maine) (7), 1868, 1876, 1884, 1889, 1894, 1898 (Box 5, Folder 260)
    - Nelson, Cleland Kinlock 1852-1917, (Ga.) (9), 1894-1896, 1901, 1903, 1907, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 261)
    - Nelson, Richard Henry 1859-1931, (Albany, N.Y.) (9), 1904, 1906, 1908, 1913-1914, 1921 (Box 5, Folder 262)
    - Newton, John Brockenbrough 1839-1897, (Va.) (4), 1886, 1892, 1896 (Box 6, Folder 263)
    - Nichols, John William 1878-, (Shanghai) (2), 1937 (Box 6, Folder 264)
    - Nichols, Shirley Hall 1884-, (Kyoto) (5), 1937, undated (Box 6, Folder 265)
    - Nichols, William Ford 1849-1924, (Cal.) (11), 1893-1895, 1899, 1902-1903, 1905, 1913, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 266)
    - Nicholson, Isaac Lea 1844-1906, (Milwaukee) (6), 1891, 1898, 1903 (Box 6, Folder 267)
    - Niles, William Woodruff 1832-1914, (N.H.) (12), 1883, 1891-1892, 1898, 1903, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 268)
    - Odenheimer, William Henry 1817-1879, (N.J.) (6), 1867, 1869, 1871, 1874, undated (Box 6, Folder 269)
    - Oldham, George Ashton 1877-, (Albany) (4), 1934, 1937, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 270)
    - Olmsted, Charles Sanford 1853-1918, (Col.) (8), 1898, 1902-1906 (Box 6, Folder 271)
    - Olmsted, Charles Tyler 1842-1924, (Cen. N.Y.) (8), 1883, 1897, 1902, 1904, 1908 (Box 6, Folder 272)
    - Onderdonk, Benjamin Tredwell 1791-1861, (N.Y.) (23), 1831-1833, 1837-1840, 1842-1844, 1852-1853, undated (Box 6, Folder 273)
    - Onderdonk, Henry Ustick 1789-1858, (Penn.) (6), 1834, 1836, 1838, 1857 (Box 6, Folder 274)
      [Convention address, 10mss.pp, 1831]
    - Osborne, Edward William 1845-1926, (Springfield, Mass.) (7), 1904, 1907-1908, 1911, 1923 (Box 6, Folder 275)
    - Otey, James Hervey 1800-1863, (Tenn.-S.C.?) (6), 1857-1858, 1860-1861 (Box 6, Folder 276)
    - Paddock, Benjamin Henry 1828-1891, (Mass.) (10), 1874, 1876, 1880, 1883, 1887, 1890, undated (Box 6, Folder 277)
    - Paddock, John Adams 1825-1894, (Wash.) (7), 1882-1883, 1893, undated (Box 6, Folder 278)
    - Paddock, Robert Lewis 1869-, (Oregon) (8), 1907-1908, 1911, 1915 (Box 6, Folder 279)
    - Page, Herman 1866-, (Mich.) (4), 1929, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 280)
    - Paret, William 1826-1911, (Md.) (13), 1883, 1886, 1890, 1893, 1895, 1898, 1902-1903, 1905, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 281)
    - Parker, Edward Melville 1855-1925, (N.H.) (7), 1906, 1911, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 282)
    - Parker, Samuel 1744-1804, (Mass.) (4), 1795, 1802, undated (Box 6, Folder 283)
    - Parsons, Edward Lambe 1868-, (Cal.) (5), 1931, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 284)
    - Partridge, Sidney Catlin 1857-1930, (Kyoto, Japan) (6), 1900, 1902, 1907, 1909, undated (Box 6, Folder 285)
    - Payne, John 1815-1874, (Africa?) (5), 1860-1861, 1867, 1871 (Box 6, Folder 286)
    - Peabody, Malcolm Endicott (Cen. N.Y.) (3), 1949, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 287)
    - Penick, Charles Clifton 1843-1914, (W. Africa), 1877, 1893-1894, 1896, 1905, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 288)
      [Sermon, 1909; the 1877 letter is written on a 2pp. printed "Eastertide" address to the West Africans]
    - Perry, James De Wolf, Jr. 1871-1947 (R.I.) (24), 1910, 1911, 1913, 1915, 1919, 1922, 1931, 1934, 1937 (Box 6, Folder 289)
    - Perry, William Stevens 1832-1898, (Iowa) (10), 1863, 1871, 1873, 1890-1891 (Box 6, Folder 290)
    - Peterkin, George William 1841-1916, (W.Va.) (8), 1884, 1902-1903, 1906, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 291)
    - Pierce, Henry Niles 1820-1899, (Ark.) (8), 1870, 1891, 1896-1898, undated (Box 6, Folder 292)
    - Pinkney, William 1810-1883, (Md.) (4), 1874, 1880-1881 (Box 6, Folder 293)
    - Pithan, Athalicio Theodoro (1), undated (Box 6, Folder 294)
    - Polk, Leonidas 1806-1864, (La.) (8), 1833, 1859, 1861-1863 (Box 6, Folder 295)
    - Porter, Archie William Noel 1885-,(Sacramento) (2), 1937 (Box 6, Folder 296)
    - Potter, Alonzo 1800-1865, (Penn.) (24), 1840, 1854-1855, 1857, 1859, 1861-1864, undated (Box 6, Folder 297)
    - Potter, Henry Codman 1835-1908, (N.Y.) (49), 1874, 1882-1891, 1896-1898, 1901, 1903-1905, undated (Box 6, Folder 298)
    - Potter, Horatio 1802-1887, (N.Y.) (20), 1854-1856, 1860, 1863, 1866, 1871-1872, 1876-1877, 1879, 1880, 1883, undated (Box 6, Folder 299)
    - Provost [Provoost], Samuel 1742-1815, (N.Y.) (6), 1786, 1789 (Box 6, Folder 300)
      [Includes a letter from Jas. Grant Wilson to Ely concerning location of the "Provoost Sermons" in print, 1900]
    - Quin, Clinton Simon (Texas) (1), 1937 (Box 6, Folder 301)
    - Quintard, Charles Todd 1824-1898, (Tenn.) (8), 1857, 1870, 1880-1881, 1887 (Box 6, Folder 302)
    - Randall, George Maxwell 1810-1873, (Col.) (7), 1866, 1868-1869, 1871, 1873 (Box 6, Folder 303)
    - Randolph, Alfred Magill 1836-1918, (S. Va.) (6), 1888, 1909 (Box 6, Folder 304)
    - Ravenscroft, John Stark 1772-1830, (N.C.) (6), 1818, 1824, 1828 (Box 6, Folder 305)
      [Sermon, Consecration of Christ's Church, Raleigh, 1829, 39mss.pp]
    - Reese, Frederick Focke 1854-, (Ga.) (8), 1907-1909, 1915, 1926-1927 (Box 6, Folder 306)
    - Reese, Theodore Irving 1873-1931, (S. Ohio) (8), 1908, 1913, 1915-1916 (Box 6, Folder 307)
    - Reifsnider, Charles Shriver (Tokyo) (3), 1937 (Box 6, Folder 308)
    - Reinheimer, Bartel Hilen 1889-1949, (Rochester) (3), 1937 (Box 6, Folder 309)
      [Newsclippings, 49]
    - Remington, William P. (E. Oregon) (2), 1937 (Box 6, Folder 310)
    - Restarick, Henry Bond 1854-1933, (Honolulu) (6), 1902-1903, 1907, 1909, 1911 (Box 6, Folder 311)
    - Rhea, Frank A. (Idaho) (2), 1950 (Box 7, Folder 312)
      [Newsclipping, n.d.]
    - Rhinelander, Philip Mercer 1869-, (Penn.) (15), 1911-1913, 1919, 1929-1931, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 313)
    - Riley, Henry Chauncey -1904, (Mexico) (6), 1876, 1883, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 314)
    - Roberts, William Blair 1881-, (S.Dak.) (10), 1937 (Box 7, Folder 315)
      [Deacon exams, 1908, n.d.]
    - Roberts, William Payne 1888-, (Shanghai) (2), 1938 (Box 7, Folder 316)
    - Robertson, Charles Franklin 1835-1893, (Mo.) (6), 1879-1882 (Box 7, Folder 317)
    - Robinson, Henry Douglas 1859-1913, (Nev.) (5), 1908-1909 (Box 7, Folder 318)
    - Rogers, Warren Lincoln 1877-, (Ohio) (2), 1933, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 319)
    - Roots, Logan Herbert 1870-,(Hankow, China) (10), 1904, 1907, 1910, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 320)
      [Newsclippings,1937]
    - Rowe, Peter Trimble 1856-1942, (Alaska) (11), 1901, 1904, 1909-1910, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 321)
    - Rulison, Nelson Somerville 1842-1897, (Cen. Penn.) (6), 1884, 1887, 1890, 1896-1897 (Box 7, Folder 322)
    - Rutledge, Francis Huger 1799-1866, (Fla.) (5), 1849, 1856, 1866 (Box 7, Folder 323)
    - Sanford, Louis Childs 1867-, (San Joaquin, Cal.) (9), 1910-1913, 1915, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 324)
    - Satterlee, Henry Yates 1843-1908, (Wash., D.C.) (11), 1883, 1892, 1898, 1900, 1905, undated (Box 7, Folder 325)
    - Scadding, Charles 1861-1914, (Oregon) (6), 1906-1907, 1911 (Box 7, Folder 326)
    - Scarborough, John 1831-1914, (N.J.) (17), 1866, 1876, 1881, 1883, 1887, 1899, 1903, 1905-1906, 1908 (Box 7, Folder 327)
    - Scarlett, William (Mo.) (2), undated (Box 7, Folder 328)
    - Schereschewsky, Samuel Isaac Joseph 1831-1906, (China) (10), 1878, 1883-1884, 1895, 1903 (Box 7, Folder 329)
      [Translation mss note, Acts 13:36 in Chinese, n.d.]
    - Schmuck, Elmer N. (WY.) (1), undated (Box 7, Folder 330)
    - Scott, Thomas Fielding 1807-1867, (Ore.) (7), 1837, 1860, 1864, 1866 (Box 7, Folder 331)
    - Seabury, Samuel 1729-1796, (Conn.)
      - Correspondence: 1785-1787, 1789-1790 (13) (Box 8, Folder 332)
      - Letterbook entries: 1784, 1790-1792; 1792-1794 (6) (Box 8, Folder 333)
      - Sermon (with letter added, n.d.): 1767(1789); Photos (4) (Box 8, Folder 334)
      - Correspondence of others: (Box 8, Box 335)
        - [G.C.?], 1769 (Box 8, Folder 335)
        - Unsigned (2), 1786 (Box 8, Folder 335)
        - William Smith, 1789 (Box 8, Folder 335)
        - Convention Committee, 1789 (Box 8, Folder 335)
        - Samuel Seabury (grandson) (9), 1827-1828, 1838 (Box 8, Folder 335)
      - Documents
        - Certification of rectorates (Box 8, Folder 336)
          - Jamaica, L.I. (2), 1757 (Box 8, Folder 336)
          - St. Peter's (2), 1767 (Box 8, Folder 336)
        - Assent to Constitution (6), 1789 (Box 8, Folder 336)
      - Documents (Oversize, Folio)
        - Yale M.A. diploma, 1751 (Box 9, Folder 337)
        - Oxford honorary degree, 1777 (Box 9, Folder 337)
        - Ordination of Charles Seabury as deacon, by Samuel Seabury, 1793 (Box 9, Folder 337)
        - Priestly ordination by Richard, Bp. of Carlisle, 1753 (Box 9, Folder 337)
        - Episcopal ordination by Scottish bishops, 1784 (Box 9, Folder 337)
        - Diaconal ordination by John, Bp of Lincoln, 1753 (Box 9, Folder 337)
        - Petition to Hartford General Assembly, 1740 (Box 9, Folder 338)
        - Petition of grievances to Conn. General Assembly, 1775 (Box 9, Folder 339)
        - "Concordate, or Bond of Union," between American and Scottish Church, signed by Seabury, Kilgour, Petrie, and Skinner, 1784 (Box 9, Folder 340)
        - Book of Common Prayer, 1770 edition with additions and revisions pasted in by Seabury (e.g. prayer for the President) (Box 9, Folder 341)
    - Seaman, Eugene Cecil 1881-, (N. Texas) (3), 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 342)
    - Sessums, Davis (La.) (6), 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 343)
    - Seymour, George Franklin 1829-1906, (Springfield, Ill.)(27), 1856, 1877-1878, 1880, 1882-1885, 1887, 1896, 1898-1899, 1902-1903, 1905-1906, undated (Box 10, Folder 344)
    - Sherrill, Henry Knox 1890-, (Mass.) (11), 1927, 1929, 1937, 1949-1950, undated (Box 10, Folder 345)
    - Shires, Henry H. (Cal.) (2), 1950 (Box 10, Folder 346)
    - Slattery, Charles Lewis 1867-1930, (Mass.) (9), 1910, 1921-1922, 1928-1929 (Box 10, Folder 347)
    - Smith, Benjamin Bosworth 1794-1884, (KY.), 1923, 1857, 1869, 1873-1876, 1880 (Box 10, Folder 348)
    - Smith, Robert 1732-1801, (S.C.) (5), 1776, 1781 (Box 10, Folder 349)
    - Southgate, Horatio 1812-1894, (Turkey) (13), 1840, 1846, 1849-1850, 1875 (Box 10, Folder 350)
      [writings, sermons: 1849, 1855, 1863, n.d.]
    - Spalding, Franklin Spencer 1865-1914, (Salt Lake City) (6), 1904, 1906-1907, undated (Box 10, Folder 351)
    - Spalding, John Franklin 1828-1902, (Col.) (8), 1876-1877, 1882, 1889 (Box 10, Folder 352)
    - Spencer, Robert Nelson (W. Mo.) (2), undated (Box 10, Folder 353)
    - Stark, Dudley Scott (Rochester) (1), undated (Box 10, Folder 354)
    - Starkey, Thomas Alfred 1818-1903, (Newark) (21), 1880, 1882-1884, 1889, 1895, 1898-1900, 1902 (Box 10, Folder 355)
    - Stearley, Wilson Reiff 1869-1941, (Newark) (5), 1918, 1922, 1937, undated (Box 10, Folder 356)
    - Sterret, Frank William 1885-, (Penn.) (2), 1937 (Box 10, Folder 357)
    - Stevens, William Bacon 1815-1887, (Penn.) (27), 1855, 1857-1858, 1862, 1865, 1874, 1876-1878, 1881, 1883, 1885, 1887 (Box 10, Folder 358)
    - Stevens, William Bertrand 1884-, (L.A., Cal.) (3), 1923, 1936-1937 (Box 10, Folder 359)
    - Stewart, George Craig 1879-, (Chicago) (7), 1917, 1931, 1935, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 360)
    - Stires, Ernest Milmore 1866-1951, (L.I.,N.Y.) (3), 1925, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 361)
    - Stone, William Murray 1866-1951, (Md.) (4), 1823, 1837 (Box 10, Folder 362)
    - Strange, Robert 1857-1914, (N.C.) (5), 1904-1905, 1908, 1910 (Box 10, Folder 363)
    - Strider, Robert Edward Lee 1887-, (W.Va.) (3), 1937, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 364)
    - Sturtevant, Harwood 1888-, (Fond du Lac, Wisc.) (3), 1936, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 365)
    - Sumner, Walter Taylor 1873-1935, (Ore.) (2), 1915, 1926 (Box 10, Folder 366)
    - Swift, Albert Ervine 1913-, (Puerto Rico) (1), 1951 (Box 10, Folder 367)
    - Taitt, Francis M. (Penn.) (1), 1937 (Box 10, Folder 368)
    - Talbot, Ethelbert 1848-1928, (Cen. Penn.) (13), 1896-1897, 1902-1903, 1905, 1913, 1919, 1925 (Box 10, Folder 369)
    - Talbot, Joseph Cruikshank 1816-1883, (Ind.) (6), 1860, 1866, 1876, 1878, 1882 (Box 10, Folder 370)
    - Taylor, Frederick William 1853-1903, (Quincy, Ill.) (5), 1902-1903 (Box 10, Folder 371)
    - Temple, Edward Arthur 1867-1924, (N. Texas) (8), 1910-1912 (Box 10, Folder 372)
    - Thomas, Albert Sidney 1873-, (S.C.) (3), 1935, 1937, 1939 (Box 10, Folder 373)
    - Thomas, Elisha Smith 1834-1895, (Kans.) (5), 1887, 1889, 1892, 1894 (Box 10, Folder 374)
    - Thomas, Nathaniel Seymour 1867-, (Wy.) (15), 1902, 1909, 1916-1917, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 375)
    - Thomas, William Matthews Merrick (S. Brazil) (4), 1942 (Box 10, Folder 376)
      [Article: "The Missionary District of Southern Brazil," 20 mss.pp]
    - Thompson, Hugh Miller 1830-1902, (Miss.) (6), 1892, 1901-1902 (Box 10, Folder 377)
    - Thomson, Arthur Conover 1871-, (S. Va.) (3), 1931, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 378)
      [Article: 1937, 1p]
    - Thurston, Theodore Payne 1867-, (E. Okla.) (8), 1911-1912, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 379)
    - Toll, William Edward 1843-1915, (Chicago) (6), 1911-1913 (Box 10, Folder 380)
    - Touret, Frank Hale 1875-, (W. Col.;Ida.) (2), 1919, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 381)
    - Tucker, Beverly Dandridge 1846-1930, (S. Va.) (7), 1905-1906, 1908-1909, 1913 (Box 10, Folder 382)
    - Tucker, Henry St. George 1874-, (Kyoto; Va.) (20), 1912-1913, 1934, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 383)
    - Tuttle, Daniel Sylvester 1837-1923, (Mo.) (22), 1874, 1886, 1902-1903, 1905-1909, 1911-1913, 1915, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 384)
      - [Orders of consecration (in alphabetical order)] (44) (Box 10, Folder 384)
      - [Letter from Rector W.A. Seward to Pres. Chester A. Arthur (re: Tuttle), 1882] (1) (Box 10, Folder 384)
    - Tyler, John Poyntz 1862-1931, (N.Dak.) (5), 1913, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 385)
    - Upfold, George 1796-1872, (Ind.) (9), 1820, 1833, 1836, 1843, 1851, 1854, 1857, 1862 (Box 10, Folder 386)
    - Urban, Ralph Ernest 1875-1935, (N.J.) (2), 1933, undated (Box 10, Folder 387)
    - Vail, Thomas Hubbard 1812-1889, (Kans.) (10), 1866, 1874, 1876, 1878-1879, 1883-1884, 1887 (Box 10, Folder 388)
    - Van Buren, James Heartt 1850-1917, (Puerto Rico) (8), 1893, 1902, 1904, 1907 (Box 10, Folder 389)
    - Van Dyck, Vedder 1889- (Vt.) (2), 1935 (Box 10, Folder 390)
    - Vincent, Boyd 1845-1935, (S. Ohio) (11), 1893, 1902, 1908, 1815-1816, 1919, 1927, undated (Box 10, Folder 391)
    - Vinton, Alexander Hamilton 1852-1911, (W. Mass.) (5), 1896, 1902-1903, undated (Box 10, Folder 392)
    - Wainwright, Jonathan Mayhew 1792-1854, (N.Y.) (9), 1837, 1845, 1852, 1854, undated (Box 11, Folder 393)
    - Walker, William David 1839-1917, (W. N.Y.) (8), 1883, 1893, 1897, 1899, 1906 (Box 11, Folder 394)
    - Ward, John Chamberlain 1873-, (Penn.) (3), 1937, 1941 (Box 11, Folder 395)
    - Washburn, Benjamin Martin 1887-, (Newark) (2), 1937 (Box 11, Folder 396)
    - Watson, Alfred Augustin 1818-1905, (E. N.C.) (9), 1873, 1891, 1899-1900 (Box 11, Folder 397)
    - Webb, William Walter 1857-1933, (Milwaukee) (8), 1905-1906, 1911, 1919, 1927 (Box 11, Folder 398)
    - Weed, Edwin Gardner 1847-1924, (Fla.) (13), 1886-1887, 1893, 1903, 1905, 1909, 1919 (Box 11, Folder 399)
    - Weeks, William Farrar 1859-1914, (Vt.) (10), 1906, 1912-1913 (Box 11, Folder 400)
    - Weller, Reginald Heber, Jr. 1857-1935, (Fond du Lac, Wisc.) (10), 1886, 1903, 1906, 1909, 1912, 1915, 1917 (Box 11, Folder 401)
    - Welles, Edward Randolph 1830-1888, (Wisc.) (7), 1874-1875, 1882, undated (Box 11, Folder 402)
    - Wells, Lemuel Henry 1841-1936, (Spokane, Wash.) (8), 1889, 1902, 1933, undated (Box 11, Folder 403)
    - Whipple, Henry Benjamin 1822-1901, (Minn.) (13), 1862-1864, 1867, 1874, 1884, 1891, 1894, 1898, 1901 (Box 11, Folder 404)
    - Whitaker, Ozi William 1830-1911, (Penn.) (6), 1890, 1892-1893, 1903 (Box 11, Folder 405)
    - White, John Chanler (Springfield, Ill.) (1), 1937 (Box 11, Folder 406)
    - White, John Hazen 1849-1925, (Ind.) (7), 1892, 1898, 1906-1907, 1911 (Box 11, Folder 407)
    - White, William 1748-1836 (7), 1789, 1795, 1811, 1816 (Box 11, Folder 408)
    - Whitehead, Cortlandt 1842-1922, (Pittsburgh) (11), 1884, 1899, 1902-1903, 1907, 1911, 1915, 1919, undated (Box 11, Folder 409)
    - Whitehouse, Henry John 1803-1874 (8), 1842, 1852-1854, 1862, 1864, 1874 (Box 11, Folder 410)
    - Whittemore, Lewis Bliss (W. Mich.) (1), 1937 (Box 11, Folder 411)
    - Whittingham, William Rollinson 1805-1879, (Md.) (29), 1841, 1844-1845, 1851, 1855, 1857, 1860-1864, 1866-1867, 1869, 1873, 1876, 1878 (Box 11, Folder 412)
    - Whittle, Francis McNeece 1823-1902, (Va.) (8), 1872, 1874, 1878, 1881, 1895 (Box 11, Folder 413)
    - Williams, Arthur Llewellyn 1853-1919, (Neb.) (7), 1903-1905, 1908 (Box 11, Folder 414)
      [Geneology: 1927]
    - Williams, Channing Moore 1829-1910, (China; Japan) (6), 1883, 1904 (Box 11, Folder 415)
    - Williams, Charles David 1860-1923, (Mich.) (7), 1906-1907, 1909-1910, 1915 (Box 11, Folder 416)
    - Williams, Gershom Mott 1857-1923, (Ill.) (10), 1903, 1908-1909, 1921 (Box 11, Folder 417)
      [Poems: "Lent," "Impromptu," 1908]
    - Williams, John, 1817-1899 (Conn.)
      - Correspondence: (35), 1853, 1858-1859, 1864, 1866-1867, 1870, 1872, 1875-1879 (Box 11, Folder 418)
      - Correspondence: (44), 1880-1889 (Box 11, Folder 419)
      - Correspondence: (29), 1890-1895, 1898, undated (Box 11, Folder 420)
      - Convention Address, excerpt, 1872 (Box 11, Folder 421)
      - Sermons (7, mss), 1854, 1868, undated (Box 11, Folder 421)
      - Doctrine of the sacraments--questions on items L to LX (9), undated (Box 11, Folder 421)